<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Kevin Janada</title><link>https://kevinjanada.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Kevin Janada</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 10:15:15 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kevinjanada.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Knowledge and Action</title><link>https://kevinjanada.github.io/posts/knowledge-and-action/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 10:15:15 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://kevinjanada.github.io/posts/knowledge-and-action/</guid><description>Studying and learning are great, but if you do not put the knowledge into action, they do not mean anything. Putting your knowledge into practice also enforces them in you. You can see whether what you learn can work when you put it to use. Then you will have more confidence in your knowledge.
Since knowledge is embodied faster when you put it into practice, learning faster is to put your knowledge into practice as quickly as possible.</description></item><item><title>You Are What You Consume</title><link>https://kevinjanada.github.io/posts/you-are-what-you-consume/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 12:43:10 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://kevinjanada.github.io/posts/you-are-what-you-consume/</guid><description>In the book Atomic Habits, James Clear wrote that you build habits by imitating the close, the many, and the powerful. The close is our friends and family; they give off an invisible peer pressure that influences our behavior. The many are the members of our group, whatever group we are in at a particular instance. When you are unsure how to act, you naturally look to others for guidance. As humans, we need to be accepted.</description></item><item><title>Anxiety and Decision Making</title><link>https://kevinjanada.github.io/posts/anxiety-and-decision-making/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 11:12:44 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://kevinjanada.github.io/posts/anxiety-and-decision-making/</guid><description>I spend a lot of my working days feeling anxious. I have been aware of this for a long time, but I have not paid attention or thought about what causes it. There are probably many different factors, like my genes, coffee, diet, etc.
One day, while running, I was listening to a lecture by Alan Watts titled &amp;ldquo;How to Make a Decision Without Having Anxiety.&amp;rdquo; And it prompted me to ask myself.</description></item><item><title>My First Post</title><link>https://kevinjanada.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 13:32:30 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://kevinjanada.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid><description>Hello people of the internet. My name is Kevin Janada, welcome to my blog.
I am a software engineer, have been for 5 years. I mostly work with web technologies, building web2 and web3 applications, specifically on the Ethereum Blockchain. I am pretty good at playing the guitar, less so on the piano, but i like playing it nonetheless. I like to learn things from books, audiobooks, podcast, videos, you name it.</description></item></channel></rss>